Guide to the Jaime Davidovich Collection MSS.155
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Jaime Davidovich Art Files
  - Subseries I: Photographs of Jaime Davidovich
    - Group photograph including Jaime Davidovich. Black and white negative, original, and larger print., ca. 1964 (Box 40, Folder 465)
    - Jaime Davidovich and Salvador Dali at Whitney Biennial. Black and white photograph and its reprinting and newspapers., 1973 (Box 40, Folder 466)
    - Portraits of Jaime Davidovich by Babette Mangolte. Black and white prints., 1979 (Box 40, Folder 467)
    - Cutout photograph of Jaime Davidovich. Black and white photograph by Babett Mangolte., 1979 (Box 40, Folder 468)
    - Photographs of Jaime Davidovich by Pamela Duffy. Black and white large format negatives and prints., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 469)
    - Photographs of Jaime Davidovich by Babette Mangolte. Black and white contact sheet., undated (Box 40, Folder 470)
    - Jaime Davidovich with porta-pack. Black and white negatives and contact sheets., undated (Box 40, Folder 471)
    - Photographs of Jaime Davidovich. Black and white negatives, contacts, and prints., undated (Box 40, Folder 472)
    - Photographs of Jaime Davidovich by Nanny Roitman., undated (Box 40, Folder 473)
    - Two small black and white portraits of Jaime Davidovich., undated (Box 40, Folder 474)
    - Family photographs, black and white contact sheet and prints., undated (Box 40, Folder 475)
    - Jaime Davidovich and Borges, black and white negative and prints., undated (Box 40, Folder 476)
    - Jaime Davidovich with Borges, color photograph., undated (Box 40, Folder 477)
    - Jaime Davidovich with TV collection. Black and white print., undated (Box 40, Folder 478)
    - Black and white contact sheet and print, color print of miscellaneous TVs. Grouped by Jaime Davidovich., undated (Box 40, Folder 479)
    - Black and white photographs of Jaime Davidovich's TV collection., undated (Box 40, Folder 480)
  - Subseries J: Press, Interviews, and Essays about Jaime Davidovich.
    - Cleveland Guide, "A Trip Into Space" article about Jaime Davidovich., 1973 (Box 40, Folder 481)
    - Akron Beacon, "New Gallery Goes Under Despite Good Performance", 1973 (Box 40, Folder 482)
    - Photocopy of Art Forum article, "Jaime Davidovich" by Carolyn Kinder Carr., 1974 (Box 40, Folder 484)
    - John Matturi essay "Jaime Davidovich". With annotations., 1979 (Box 40, Folder 485)
    - John Matturi essay, "Jaime Davidovich" in plastic binder., 1979 (Box 40, Folder 486)
    - Video Magazine, "Home is Where the Art Is", 1980 (Box 41, Folder 487)
    - "Miscellaneous Articles 1982" Includes photographs and photocopies of articles relating to Jaime Davidovich's work. (Box 41, Folder 488)
    - Cahiers du Cinema, made in USA. Center for Media Art Festival de Video, Paris., 1982 (Box 41, Folder 489)
    - Ryuko-Tsushin, profile of Jaime Davidovich., 1983 (Box 41, Folder 490)
    - The Art of Video, Spanish series includes an interview with Jaime Davidovich., 1989 (Box 41, Folder 491)
    - "Tape as Art and Art on Tape" interview of Jaime Davidovich by J.R. Blevins. Transcript and black and white photographs., undated (Box 41, Folder 492)
    - "Artistas Argentinos en el Exterior" questions and Jaime Davidovich's responses., undated (Box 41, Folder 493)
    - Interview, Jaime Davidovich and J. Handham., undated (Box 41, Folder 494)
- Series II: Artists TV Network
  Subseries A: ATN publicity includes promotional materials such as posters and brochures, and press. Subseries B: Documentation of Organizational Activity includes materials such as photographs, distribution catalogues, and conference proceedings. Subseries C: TV Magazine includes materials related to the production of the magazine such as mock-ups. Subseries D: Correspondence includes collected correspondence organized alphabetically by organization, event, or recipient. Subseries E: Organizational Materials includes contracts, grant materials, and other documents relevant to the organization's functioning. Subseries F: Financial Materials includes bank statements, ledgers, and tax information concerning the Artists Television Network.
  - Subseries A: Artists TV Network Publicity
    - Video-Art, a TV infant, Is shooting for Prime Time", International Herald Tribune., 1978 (Box 41, Folder 495)
    - "TV: 'SoHo' programs on video art", New York Times, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 496)
    - "Cable Picks" Soho TV news, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 497)
    - Artists TV press, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 498)
    - Artists Television Network, program schedule, Friday Night Double Feature of "The Live! Show", 1983 (Box 41, Folder 499)
    - New York Culture Map, includes Artists TV Network. Japanese., 1983 (Box 41, Folder 500)
    - Press, Sao Paulo Bienal. Mentions ATN., 1983 (Box 41, Folder 501)
    - Conference hosted by the Institute of American Studies, Barcelona, Press., 1983 (Box 41, Folder 502)
    - SoHo TV brochure - Advertising services, undated (Box 41, Folder 506)
  - Subseries B: Documentation of Organizational Activity
    - Qube Project, "Artists Television Network Qube Project Report., 1979 (Box 41, Folder 508)
    - Back and white stills, some with descriptions, ca. 1980 (Box 41, Folder 509)
    - Perspectives on the Avant-Garde, black and white photographs and tape description., 1981 (Box 41, Folder 510)
    - Institute of American Studies, Barcelona, USA TV exhibit and conference schedule, programming information, notes, and essays., 1983 (Box 41, Folder 512)
    - Institute of American Studies, Barcelona, USA TV exhibit and conference. Photographs., 1983 (Box Binder 8, Folder data_value_missing_b4ee7c94a28bf317483da82ea319ab64)
    - From TV to Video, Bologna. Exhibition catalogue., 1984 (Box 41, Folder 513)
    - Video Tape Review, Video Data Bank., 1986 (Box 41, Folder 514)
    - TV Graffiti and SoHo TV" color slides in binder., undated (Box Binder 9, Folder data_value_missing_880122747386fadc5029e2a7528cc994)
    - "SoHo, SoHo TV, Live! Show" color slides in binder., undated (Box Binder 10, Folder data_value_missing_9347dc2d718b33975be792c18d670452)
    - Scrap Book including Artists Television Network, SoHo TV, and the Live! Show., undated (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_48f27647c924a6392c957dea733aef58)
    - Black and white negatives, contat sheet, and prints. TV stills, including Marshall Efron with the Fluxus Mask., undated (Box 12, Folder 515)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. TV Stills., undated (Box 12, Folder 516)
    - Black and white negatives, contact sheet, and prints. TV stills, includes photos of Laurie Anderson with her violin., undated (Box 12, Folder 517)
    - Black and white negatives, contact sheet, and prints. Photographs of Jaime Davidovich, labeled "Artists TV" on reverse., undated (Box 12, Folder 518)
    - Black and white photographic video stills, "SoHo Television" and "Welcome to Videoland", undated (Box 12, Folder 519)
    - Black and white negatives, contact sheet, and prints. Includes video stills of Jaime Davidovich and Richard Foreman, among others., undated (Box 12, Folder 520)
    - Black and white large format negative and print. Stamped, "The Artists Television Network", undated (Box 12, Folder 521)
    - Black and white large format negatives and prints., undated (Box 12, Folder 522)
    - Artists Television Network programming catalog., undated (Box 12, Folder 523)
    - Artists Television Project at Univeristy of Iowa. Publicity brochure., undated (Box 12, Folder 524)
    - Video Art on Qube, proposal., undated (Box 12, Folder 525)
  - Subseries C: TV Magazine.
    - Cover art, black and white photograph with measuring annotations., undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Reverand Deacon B. Peachy, notes and graphic., undated (Box 12, Folder 529)
    - John Wilcock, notes, graphic., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 530)
    - Potato Wolf, graphic and notes., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 531)
    - Nick Yanni, graphic, notes, photocipies., undated (Box 12, Folder 532)
    - Black and white photographs with annotations, used in TV magazine., undated (Box 12, Folder 533)
    - TV magazine, volume 1, number 1., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 534)
  - Subseries D: Correspondence
    - "Films on Art" Rotterdam festival correspondence., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 535)
    - Institute of American Studies, Barcelona. Correspondence regarding the TV-USA-Spain conference., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 536)
    - The Kitchen Cable Review Lounge, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 537)
    - NEA correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 538)
    - Jaime Davidovich to Nam June Paik., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 539)
    - "Personal, Artists Television Network". Correspondence between members regardingIngrid Wiegand incident., 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 540)
    - Qube Project correspondence., 1979 (Box 12, Folder 541)
    - State of New York, Department of State. Correspondence regarding fiscal year 1987 (Box 12, Folder 542)
    - Taxes, 1986. Correspondence with Art institutions., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 543)
    - TV Magazine, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 544)
    - University of Iowa, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 545)
    - University of Iowa, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 546)
    - University of Iowa, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 547)
    - University of Iowa, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 548)
    - University of Iowa, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 549)
  - Subseries E: Organizational Materials
    - ATN Research and Development Project, final report by Leandra Strobing for NEA., 1978 (Box 12, Folder 550)
    - SoHo TV Contract between ATN and Jaime Davidovich., 1979 (Box 12, Folder 551)
    - Agreement for Channel use between Manhattan Cable and ATN, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 552)
    - Manhattan Cable TV community programming handbook, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 553)
    - ATN Introduction and Supplementary Material., undated (Box 12, Folder 554)
    - ATN Introduction and Supplementary Material., undated (Box 12, Folder 555)
    - University of Iowa, miscellaneous materials., undated (Box 12, Folder 556)
    - Miscellaneous works on paper, SoHo TV., undated (Box 12, Folder 557)
  - Subseries F: Financial materials
    - IRS Exemption Paperwork, Artists Television Network., 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 558)
    - ATN Tax returns, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 559)
    - ATN laminated tax exempt certificate, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 560)
    - ATN tax returns, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 561)
    - ATN Ledger., 1980-1985 (Box 14, Folder data_value_missing_ad6f2cb1498d6c5aac1ffbf86c34832b)
    - ATN Tax returns, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 562)
    - ATN Banking, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 563)
    - ATN taxes and CPA materials, 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 564)
    - Forms regarding withholding tax from employees and disability insurance., 1983-1987 (Box 12, Folder 565)
    - ATN taxes, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 566)
    - ATN Citibank statements and cancelled checks., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 567)
    - ATN Citibank statements and cancelled checks., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 569)
    - ATN income tax., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 571)
    - ATN Citibank statements and cancelled checks. Removed from account book in folder 573., 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 573)
    - ATN account and check book. Includes paperwork from 1986. (Box 12, Folder 574)
    - ATN income tax., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 575)
    - ATN Citibank statements, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 576)
    - ATN Citibank statements., 1987 (Box 12, Folder 577)
- Series III: The Live! Show
  Series III includes materials relating to the production, promotion, and exhibition of The Live! Show. Subseries A: Production Materials includes notes, sketches and other materials connected to the production of the Live! Show. Subseries B: Design, includes promotional materials for the Live! Show designed by Jaime Davidovich. Subseries C: Photographs contains photographic documentation of The Live! Show. Subseries D: Press and Publicity contains posters, invitations, and press materials related to The Live! Show. Subseries E: Exhibition and Distribution Catalogs includes materials connected to museum exhibitions and commercial distribution of The Live! Show. Subseries F: Correspondence includes letters and written inquries.
  - Subseries A: production and presentation materials
    - Live Show Script, Saludos Amigos and Dr. Videovich call in., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 579)
    - Live Show Format, May 21 1982. (Box 12, Folder 580)
    - Live! Show format, Mayt 28 1982 (Box 12, Folder 581)
    - Live! Show format, January 14 1983. (Box 12, Folder 582)
    - Live Show Format,January 28, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 583)
    - Live! Show format, January 21 1983 (Box 12, Folder 584)
    - Sao Paulo Bienal, notes and manuscripts., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 585)
    - Live! Show agenda and format for program at Cleveland Contemporary Art Center., 1984 (Box 12, Folder 586)
    - Hardcover book with notes, photographs, diagrams and other elements in preparation for American Museum of the Moving Image Exhibition., 1989 (Box 12, Folder 587)
    - "Dr. Videovich Real World Workshop" notes and agenda., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 588)
    - The Live! Show production notebook., undated (Box 12, Folder 590)
    - Contents of the Live! Show production binder. Includes photographs, program descriptions, show format scripts, and mailing list among other items., undated (Box 12, Folder 591)
    - Live! Show format script,August 13, undated (Box 12, Folder 592)
    - Live! Show format script, September 24, undated (Box 12, Folder 593)
    - Program descriptions and model release forms, undated (Box 12, Folder 594)
  - Subseries B: Design
    - Live! Show letterhead, undated (Box 12, Folder 596)
    - AMMI Live! Show retrospective, black and white photographs and production snapshots annotated with scale., undated (Box 12, Folder 597)
    - Masters for AMMI The Live! Show retrospective catalog., undated (Box 12, Folder 598)
    - AMMI Live! Show retrospective, catalog mock up., undated (Box 12, Folder 599)
    - AMMI Live! Show retrospective, program notes mock up, undated (Box 12, Folder 600)
  - Subseries C: Photographs
    - Black and white photograph, TV still of art lesson., undated (Box 13, Folder 601)
    - Black and white photograph, TV still of Dr. Videovich, "Call Now", undated (Box 13, Folder 602)
    - Black and white photograph, TeeVee, undated (Box 13, Folder 603)
    - Black and white photograph, video still, "Tel Aviv", undated (Box 13, Folder 604)
    - Collected black and white photographs of Jaime Davidovich's work, including Live! Show, Evita, Welcome to Videoland, and Video Painting., undated (Box 13, Folder 605)
    - Black and white photographs, still of The Live! Show., undated (Box 13, Folder 606)
    - Black and white photographs, Dr. Videovich in TV costume and Jaime Davidovich with TV collection., undated (Box 13, Folder 607)
    - Black and white photographs. Images labeled "Jaime Davidovich, The Live! Show" folder labeled "Live! Show AMMI", undated (Box 13, Folder 608)
    - Black and white photographs of Dr. Videovich., undated (Box 13, Folder 609)
    - Black and white negatives and photographs. Collected stills from the Live! Show. Grouped by Jaime Davidovich, divided into two parts. Part 1 of 2., undated (Box 13, Folder 610)
    - Black and white negatives and photographs. Collected stills from the Live! Show. Grouped by Jaime Davidovich, divided into two parts. Part 2 of 2., undated (Box 13, Folder 611)
    - Three black and white photographs and one color photograph of Dr. Videovich and foam televisions., undated (Box 13, Folder 612)
    - Three black and white video stills of the Live! Show and one color photograph of small foam Sony Television sculpture., ca. 1982. (Box 13, Folder 613)
    - Black and white video still of the Live! Show with Dr. Videovich and C.A Klonarides. Removed from frame by Fales Library., undated (Box 13, Folder 614)
    - 2 black and white video stills of The Live! Show, 1 black and white image of Jaime Davidovich watching TV., undated (Box 13, Folder 615)
    - Black and white negatives, contact sheet, and print. Dr. Videovich, undated (Box 13, Folder 616)
    - Black and white negatives, contact sheet, and print. The Live! Show., undated (Box 13, Folder 617)
    - Color photographs, undated (Box Binder 17)
  - Subseries D: Press and Publicity Materials
    - Live! Show Advertisement, undated (Box 13, Folder 618)
    - Live! Show Advertisement, undated (Box 13, Folder 619)
    - Live! Show press release, undated (Box 13, Folder 621)
    - On Cable magazine, October 1982, Includes Manhattan Cable Television Schedule: Live! Show on Channel J. (Box 13, Folder 622)
    - Collected Live! Show press and blank storyboard., 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 623)
    - Live! Show press, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 624)
    - Sao Paulo Bienal, press, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 625)
    - Two copies, Mensajes y Medios n. 10, includes article "Jaime Davidovich: El Humor como Arma de Reflexion", 1990 (Box 13, Folder 627)
  - Subseries E: Exhibition and Distribution Catalogs.
    - Bienal de Sao Paulo, Catalogo Geral [Live! Show on p. 129], 1983 (Box 13, Folder 628)
    - Beinal de Sao Paulo, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 629)
    - Bienal de Sao Paulo, "New Metaphors/Six Alternatives". Includes program, press releases, and other programmatic materials., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 630)
    - Cleveland Contemporary Art Center, "Cleveland Revisited", 1984 (Box 13, Folder 631)
    - 1984 A Video Review, "So There, Orwell" Catalog and schedule. (Box 13, Folder 632)
    - Word-Wide Video Festival. Dr. Videovich tape and Evita Tape., 1984 (Box 13, Folder 633)
    - ArtCom, Utah Arts Festival "Video Environments" includes Schedule, catalog, press release among other programmatic materials., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 634)
    - "On Arts and Artists", Video Data Bank. Distribution catalog., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 635)
    - Art Com Media Distribution Catalog, number 1., 1988 (Box 13, Folder 636)
    - The Live! Show Retrospective at AMMI, programs, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 637)
    - The Live! Show retrospective at AMMI, catalog., 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 638)
    - The Live Show, exhibit at AMMI, program and 5 color slides labeled "Digital Diaspora". Grouped by Jaime Davidovich., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 639)
    - "Kill Win", Art Metropole video archive catalogue., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 641)
    - "Next Five Minutes Video Catalog" Festival on Tactical Television. Includes "Saludos Amigos", 1993 (Box 13, Folder 642)
    - Famous for 30 Seconds: Artists in the Media at Artists Space. Inlcudes "SoHo TV presents: The Live! Show", undated (Box 13, Folder 643)
  - Subseries F: Correspondence
    - The Live! Show and Manhattan Cable, TV. NY State cable commission hearings. Includes correspondence and some paperwork., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 644)
    - Bienal de Sao Paulo, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 645)
    - Cleveland Contemporary Art Center, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 646)
    - Universidada Campinas, Brazil regarding using "Dr Videovich" and "Videokitsch" works in a multimedia archive., 1996 (Box 13, Folder 647)
    - Jaime Davidovich to Kim Smith. File labeled "Saludos Ameigos '85, N.J. Paik.", 1986 (Box 13, Folder 648)
    - Email correspondence with J.P. Herzberg. Subject line "Herzberg Draft", with annotations., 2000 (Box 13, Folder 649)
- Series IV: Video recordings
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes video art created by Jaime Davidovich, and videotapes created in collaboration with others as part of Artists TV Network and The !Live Show. This series also includes video documentation of events and artworks shot by Davidovich, in particular the original footage Davidovich shot of Gordon Matta-Clark's "Fake Estates" project, entitled "Queens 1975". All original videotapes acquired as part of the Jaime Davidovich Collection have been preserved.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
  - Bath, 1970's; cuid44186
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: 36 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0144)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44203 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0143)
  - Surveillance, 1970's; cuid44187
    Duration: 33 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0150)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44205 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0149)
  - 1. Sidewalk With Stuart Sherman 2. Frame, 1970's; cuid44188
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
    Duration: 22 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0171)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44212 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0170)
  - Entrances - Final, 1970's; cuid44189
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd ID: 155.0174)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44213 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0173)
  - Road / Jaime Davidovich, 1972; ID: 155.0141
    Duration: 20 minutes; Original format:1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0141)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44202 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0140)
  - 1. "Road" 2. "Blue/ Red/ Yellow", 1972; 1974; ID: 155.0210
    Duration:53 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0210)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44225 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0209)
  - 1. "Two Windows" by Jaime Davidovich 2. Excerpts From Videotapes 1972-1976 ("Road, 1972"; Blue-Red-Yellow, 1974"), 1976; 1974; ID: 155.0147
    Duration: 48 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0147)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44204 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0146)
  - New York Project I Panel, 1975; ID: 155.0159
    Duration: 28 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0159)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44208 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0158)
  - 3 Mercer Street Store with Stuart Sherman, 1975; ID: 155.0163
    Duration: 29 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0163)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44209 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0161)
  - Billboards to 143, 1975; ID: 155.0168
    Duration: 27 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0168)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44211 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0167)
  - 1. NY Project 1 2. 3 Level Dichotomy, 1975; ID: 155.0180
    Duration: 25 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0180)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44215 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0179)
  - 1. Open Show 112 Greene Street 2. TV Wall 1975, ID: 155.0216
    Duration: 23 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0216)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44227 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.00215)
  - Baseboard, 1975; ID: 155.0288
    Duration: 14 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0288)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44248 (Box Shared Fales PM 47, Digital betacam 155.0287)
  - Gordon Matta-Clark, Land Queens (1974 as per Jane Crawford, Matta-Clark's widow), 1975; ID: 155.0324
    Duration: 14 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copies (Box Shared Fales 147, Dvd 155.0324, Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0097, 155.0098, 155.0099)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44258 (Box Shared Fales PM 48, Digital betacam 155.0323)
  - Interior / Synapse, 1976; ID: 155.0153
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0153)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44206 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0152)
  - Clocktower, August, 1976; ID: 155.0165